LOGAN COLLINS

Senior Back-End Developer

+1-516-654-4426

@ hermes8527@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

Brewlabs

= 04/2023 - 03/2024

https://brewlabs.info/

- Created the company landing page using React from the Figma design, featuring simple yet elegant components and smooth animations
- Developed a bot in Node.js to fetch cryptocurrency assets and price history to show in the TradingView Chart
- Worked in the NFT Marketplace backend project in Node.js to retrieve NFT sale and metadata

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

SparkWorld*

= 04/2022 - 03/2023

- Led a team of four back-end developers to develop the back-end APIs to add, update and retrieve sale data in NFT Marketplace using the testdriven development approach in Golang
- Developed a bot in Golang to get NFT sale data and metadata from other NFT Marketplaces on Avalanche and store them in MongoDB as a subproject of NFT Aggregator
- Developed RESTful APIs in Golang to show NFT sale data in specific periods and find appropriate NFTs with specific prices, attributes and names

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

Satang Technologies

m 04/2020 - 03/2022

- Worked in company landing page project to provide APIs to get service and product list
- Designed and developed Firo Bridge in Golang to synchronize data between the Firo chain and FiroVM chain and store transaction data in PostgreSQL database to enable Smart Contracts on Firo like Ethereum
- Took part in the Asset Tokenizer project as a back-end developer.
 Collaborated with Smart Contract and front-end team to provide APIs for uploading real-estate data on storage service and get asset and sale data

Senior Full Stack Developer

Polisport

= 04/2019 - 03/2020

https://polisport.com/, https://polisportvirtualtour.com/

- · Joined the company as a Full Stack Web Developer
- Worked in backend team to retrieve products and services data to show in landing page and product lists page in Node.js and provided Swagger documentation for my APIs
- · Wrote unit test scripts for the back-end APIs using Mocha and Chai
- Led Polisport Virtual Tour Project and designed backend APIs to get product and room info to show in virtual tour website

Full Stack Developer

Canary Technologies

= 04/2016 - 03/2019

Phttps://glassbororentals.com/, https://ventano.de/

- During my six-month internship as a developer, I gained valuable insights into the company culture and development methodologies
- In the Glassboro Rentals project, I worked with two backend developers to design a MySQL database and write queries to retrieve data for frontend
- Designed a MySQL database and contributed to three pages using Laravel framework as a Full Stack Developer in the Ventano project

SUMMARY

A seasoned back-end developer with 8+ years of experience in the web development industry. What sets me apart is the ability to learn new technologies, passion for the product and keen eye for detail.

I always create detailed workflows, progress stepby-step, and conduct thorough testing to ensure accuracy and timely development.

I enjoy proposing new ideas, wearing different hats, and collaborating with others to achieve success.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

GPA

DePaul Unversity

= 2012 - 2016

Chicago, IL

3.9 / 4.0

SKILLS

Framework	S		
Node.js	Nest.js	Larav	el
ASP.NET	Django		
Languages			
JavaScript	TypeScript		Golang
Python	C#		
3rd party lib	oraries		
Stripe F	PayPal	OAuth2	-
Communica	ntion		
RESTful API Web		Socket	GraphQL
Database			

Database

MongoDB MySQL PostgreSQL

Version Control Systems

Git GitHub GitLab Bitbucket

Cloud Services

AWS GCP Microsoft Azure